[Music]
Welcome to Weekly Stock Discovery, where every
week you'll find a hot stock that
could move the market.  So friends,
our stock of the week is ICICI
LBARD General Insurance, a trusted name
in the insurance sector and now the charts are also giving
clear signals of a breakout.
If we talk about technical analysis, then
looking at the chart, the stock has given a
breakout of cup and handle pattern on the daily time frame.
That too with strong volumes
and bonus the stock is sustaining above 200 EMA.  That is,
with a solid bullish sign.  Now let's talk about its levels from where
we should buy it and work.  So the
buy zone for this stock will be in the
range of ₹1950 to
₹1960.  Its target will be the first
target of this stock will be 2020.  The second
target will be ₹100 and in this you should
work by placing a stop loss which will be ₹1900.  This
trade is a swing call.  Meaning a
perfect opportunity for short to medium term.
If we talk about ICICI Blar General
Insurance stock, then today we observed a very
good rally.  This stock has
hit a high of around 2013 today.  So you are
requested that if you
get a chance to make a fresh entry once again, then
definitely do it in this stock.  Its next
target is visible.
Follow Commodity News for more such innovative stocks and analysis.